Many lives. Unlimited potential.
Infinite is a science fiction, action, adventure film directed by Antoine Fuqua.
Evan McCauley has skills he never learned and
memories of places he has never visited.
Self-medicated and on the brink of a mental breakdown, a secret group that call
themselves “Infinites” come to his rescue, revealing that his memories are real.
Evan McCauley, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Bathurst 2020, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Nora Brightman, played by Sophie Cookson.
Artisan, played by Jason Mantzoukas.
Bathurst 1985, played by Rupert Friend.
Porter, played by Toby Jones.
Infinite is a 2021 American science fiction action film directed by Antoine Fuqua, from a
screenplay written by Ian Shorr based on a story by Todd Stein (itself adapted from D.
Eric Maikranz's 2009 novel The Reincarnationist Papers).
The film stars Mark Wahlberg, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Sophie Cookson, Jason
Mantzoukas, Rupert Friend, Toby Jones and Dylan O'Brien.
The film was digitally released on Paramount+ on June 10, 2021, following delays from
its original August 2020 theatrical release due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
It received negative reviews from critics who criticized the performances and
screenplay, with some comparing it unfavorably with other films like The Matrix.
The film received three nominations at the Golden
Raspberry Awards, including Worst Picture.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, secret
organization, reincarnation, memories, matter of fact.
The tone is thought_provoking.